Remember...
牢记
But doctor, I remember everything.
但是医生  我记得所有事情
People forget things when they have Alzheimer's.
人们患有老年痴呆症时会忘记事物
But sooner or later, I will forget things, right?
但是迟早我会忘记事情的  对吗？
All my memories, experiences will be erased, they will go away.
我所有的记忆  经验将被抹去  将会消失
What will happen to me? What will happen to my personality?
我会怎样？我的性格会怎样？
Our peaceful, sweet Agah scolding the waiter.
我们和平  友善的Agah骂了服务员
I can't believe it.
我不敢相信
I chose you from 50 girls.
我从五十个女孩中选了你
It wasn't because your father was a cop.
不是因为你父亲是警察
How does it feel to be the only woman
作为唯一的女人感觉如何
working in an homicide bureau with 140 staff members?
在拥有140名员工的凶杀局工作？
I've never felt so good.
我从来没有这么好过
Dad, I'm getting a divorce.
爸  我要离婚了
It's over, I can't tolerate this man no more. We are moving back with Deva.
结束了  我再也不能容忍这个男人了  我和Deva准备搬回去
I'm not doing anything, Naimhan. I haven't done anything.
我什么也没做  Naimhan  我什么也没做
You did it. You and them.
你到了  你和他们
All of you.
你们所有人
Nevra, why did you bother to come here?
Nevra  你为什么要来这里？
We could come to you!
我们可以去找你！
Where do you know me from?
你从哪里认识我的？
Who doesn't know you?
谁不认识你
You're famous.
你很有名
Anyway.
无论如何
What's up? What's the matter?
你来这有什么事吗
If it's within our power, we'll take care of it.
如果在我们的能力范围内  我们一定配合
You'll get cancer.
你会得癌症的
Why did you set fire to the courthouse?
你为什么放火烧法庭？
I didn't do it.
我没做
You were arrested.
你是因此被捕的
Give a dog a bad name.
我给狗起了个坏名字
I'll beat the rap in the first session, I'm waiting for it.
我将在第一节中获胜  我在等着呢
I know you are,
我知道
but you have set fire to it before.
但是你以前放过火
Seven years ago.
七年前
That's different. I served my time.
那不一样  我已经服了刑
Do you know this man?
你认识这个人吗？
Look closely. His file was in that building.
仔细看看  他的文件在那栋大楼里
They saw his case there.
他们在那里看到他的案子
Don't know him. Never seen him.
不认识他  从没见过
Okay.
好的
What did this man do?
这个人做了什么？
- Killed a judge. - Damn.
-杀了一名法官 -牛逼啊
I thought about it once,
我也曾经想过
but then I said, never mind. It's not worth it.
但后来有想了想  算了吧  不值得
Didn't do it.
所以就没做
But you set fire to the courthouse where you worked as a bailiff.
但是你在做法警的时候放火烧了法院
It's a courthouse, love.
那是法院  亲爱的
It burns, floods, even collapses.
它燃烧  淹没甚至倒塌
Evidence gets lost.
证据丢失
Case files fly away.
案卷消失了
Let me tell you something, love.
让我告诉你一些事  亲爱的
They must have found a wretched man like me,
他们一定找到了一个像我这样可怜的人
gave him some money, so he sparked a match.
给了他一些钱  于是才点燃了火柴
Look, love.
亲爱的
My town is famous for two things.
我的家乡以两件事而闻名
The blackest of grape, and the darkest of man.
最黑的葡萄和最黑的人
That building burns down every five or ten years, see?
那栋建筑物每隔五到十年就被烧毁  明白吗？
Let's see if you can find the person who hired the arsonist, if you have the balls.
如果你有胆量的话看看你是否能找到雇了纵火犯的人
Then you'll find out. I'll be shouting in front of the building.
然后你会发现我会在大楼前大喊
But they'll all be free before I finish my words!
但是在我说完这些话之前  他们都是无罪的！
And you'll be alone, too!
而且你也会孤军奋战
The defendant, Nevra Elmas! The plaintiff, Nevra Elmas!
被告是Nevra Elmas!！原告也是Nevra Elmas!
See how you like that?
你觉得怎么样?
- What are you doing? - You're up.
-你在做什么？-你醒了
But why did you leave your bed?
但是你为什么要下床？
And you took out your IV needle.
还取出了静脉注射针
Come here.
过来
We must alert the nurses. They told us to call when you woke up.
我们得告诉护士  他们告诉我要在你醒来时打电话
Where's the car?
汽车在哪里？
- What car? - My car, of course. Where is it?
-什么车？-当然是我的车  在哪里？
A tow truck removed it. They gave us an address.
拖车把它拖走了  他们给了一个地址
The police gave mom a piece of paper with the address.
警察给了妈妈一张纸  上面写着地址
Pick up that paper. We'll get the car.
去拿到那张纸  我们去取车
- Now? - Yes.
-现在吗？-是的
But you just left intensive care.
但是你刚从重症监护室出来
They took you to a room, and you almost regained your consciousness.
他们带你去了一个房间  差不多已经恢复意识了
- So? - You mumbled something but we didn't hear.
-然后呢？-你喃喃自语但我们没听清
How? What did I say?
怎么说？我怎么说？
A cat named Munir or something. You asked about him.
一只叫Munir的猫还是什么的  你问到过它
- You asked if we fed him. - Huh.
-你问我们有没有给它喂食 -嗯……
Grandpa. Don't you remember anything?
爷爷  你什么都不记得了吗
How you came to the hospital?
你怎么到医院来的？
You had an angiogram.
你做了血管造影
I remember. I remember everything.
我记得  我都记得
- Come, let's get the car. - What will you do with it?
-来吧  让我们去取车 -你取车做什么？
I can't leave the car there. It's a memento from Mebrure.
我不能把车停在那里  那是Mebrure留给我的纪念品
That's your grandma's car. Come on.
那是你奶奶的车  来吧
Slowly. This way.
这边走
- There goes my head again. - Evening, sir.
-我的头疼又来了-先生  晚上好
Good evening, son. Take me slowly.
晚上好  小伙子  慢点走
- Okay. What's wrong? - My head's spinning.
-怎么了？-我的头好晕
The doctor says walk, but what good is walking?
医生说要多走路  走路有什么好处？
Your slippers... Where are we going?
你没穿拖鞋……我们去哪里？
- We'll get the keys. - Grandpa...
-我们去拿钥匙 -爷爷
Dad.
爸
Dad, are you awake? I'll alert the nurses.
爸  你醒了  我去叫护士
- No, mom. The nurses know. - They do?
-不用  妈妈  护士已经知道了 -他们知道吗？
They told him to rest. The doctor will see him tomorrow.
他们叫他先休息  医生明天再来看他
I'm all right, sweetie.
我很好  亲爱的
You gave us such a scare.
你吓到我们了
What were you doing there at that time of night?
晚上的时候你在那儿干什么?
On the other side of the city.
在城市的另一边
You left the house, and didn't tell us anything.
你离开家  什么都没告诉我们
Where were you going?
你去哪里了？
I don't know how to tell you this.
我不知道该怎么开口
I wish I could have said before... Somehow.
我应该早点告诉你们的……
You have the right to know.
你们应该知道
People sometimes
人啊  有时候
go into a wholly different mood.
会陷入完全不同的状态
They do things they wouldn't dream of.
做他们梦寐以求的事情
Even I can't recognize myself sometimes.
有时候甚至我都不认识自己
Wondering how I'd done something.
想着自己为什么会做这些事
But I did.
但是我还是做了
They happened. All of it.
都做了
You'd hear about it one day, anyway.
你们总有一天会听说的
I'd rather you hear it from me than anybody else.
我宁愿你们听我说  而不是听别人说
And then...
然后……
It's your decision, my child.
决定权在你们  孩子
I'm your father. And I'm your grandfather.
我是你的父亲  我是你的祖父
Don't you forget that, okay?
不要忘记这点  好吗？
I'm in love, sweetheart.
我恋爱了  亲爱的
- You're in love? - I have a girlfriend.
-你恋爱了吗 -我交了一个女朋友
I was at her place that night.
那天晚上我在她家
I was on my way back.
我在回去的路上
You were on your way...
你在路上
What are you saying, dad?
爸  你在说什么
- We made love until morning. - Ew! What?
-我们做爱直到天明 -呕！什么？
Key's still in the ignition, mate!
钥匙还插着呢！
- You know how to drive? - We won't be driving it.
-你会开车吗？-我们不开它
- What will we do? - We'll wreck it to shit.
-那我们干嘛？-我们要搞坏它
Sit down. You're making me dizzy.
坐下  你把我晃晕了
And? What happened to the courthouse?
怎么？法院发生了什么事？
- Who burned it down? - It looks like the mob, for now.
-谁把它烧了？-目前看来是黑帮做的
Didn't I tell you?
你看我说什么了？
We had a bet.
我们打赌
Don't celebrate yet. It's not certain.
别高兴的太早  还没确定呢
I think that man, Tufan, did it.
我认为是那个叫Tufan的男人做的
But that man, I don't know...
但是那个男人  我不清楚……
What?
什么？
Clean since he got out of jail.
他出狱之后做事一直很干净
What did he has to do with that judge?
他和那个法官有什么关系？
If only I knew.
我要是知道就好了
Let me tell you.
让我告诉你
If there's no ties between the victim and the killer,
如果受害者和杀手之间没有联系
then it's a hired gun, sweetheart.
那很可能是借刀杀人  亲爱的
He's conducting somebody else's business.
他在给做别人的事
Yes?
喂？
Where?
在哪？
On my way.
我这就过去
Another body, right?
又一具尸体  对吗？
See you later.
我走了
Of course.
当然
Who's heard of a letter with one sentence?
谁写信只写一句话？
That son of a bitch will keep writing. Nevra!
那个凶手会继续写的  Nevra!
What is it, dad?
爸爸  怎么了
The man's writing for you to read it.
这个男人在写给你看
- Yeah, so? - So you write him back.
-是  然后呢？ -你给他回信
The doctor will be here to see you in half an hour.
医生会在半小时之内过来给你检查
I hope he comes soon and lets me go. I'm tired.
希望他快点来  让我回家  我很累
In bed all day, with nothing to do.
整天躺在床上  无所事事
You didn't bring anything to read, either.
你也没带任何书可以读
Where's your mom?
你妈妈呢？
Out. Eating something.
在外面吃饭
- You have money? - I do.
-你有钱吗？-我有
Get me something to read.
去买本书来给我看
- Okay, but... - There has to be a bookstore.
-可以  但是 -这附近肯定有书店
I'll wait for the doctor.
我要等医生过来
No, no. You go now. Now.
不  不  你现在去
- Let me take you to your room. - I can go myself.
-我带你回房间-我可以自己走
You go, son.
你去吧  孩子
- But what do you want me to buy? - Well...
-你要我买什么书？-嗯……
The book is called Life Is Traffic. Buy me that.
书名叫做《人生就是交通》
- Okay. - Go ahead.
-好的 -去吧
- Get better soon. - Thank you.
-祝你早日康复 -谢谢
Terrible thing, being ill.
生病太可怕了
I hope you get well soon.
我希望你早日康复
I'm also...
我也……
He won't wake up.
他听不见的
Huh.
哦
Yes.
是
Okay then.
好吧
Have a good day.
祝你有美好的一天
- I'm here to visit him. - You don't say?
-我是来拜访他的 -真的吗？
How do you know him?
你怎么认识他的？
I ONLY TRUST HER. BECAUSE NEVRA UNDERSTANDS ME.
我只相信她  因为Nevra了解我
- Are those your brothers? - Yes.
-那是你的兄弟们吗？-是的
And what do they do?
他们怎么样？
- They get high. - That much is clear.
-他们长得很高 -是的
- And they make kites. - Was the car right there?
-他们会做风筝 -汽车在那儿吗？
No. It was over there.
不  在那边
All right, kid. Take the boy.
好吧  孩子 把他带走吧
- Must've been followed. - Yeah.
-一定是被人跟踪了 -是的
Another casing, sir.
又找到一个  先生
Did his job with one bullet in his first. Now fired six times.
第一次只用了一颗子弹  这次用了六颗
Then again, he also shot an aquarium in the first one.
并且他还在第一次射中了鱼缸
The victim has two entry wounds.
受害人有两处伤口
Did his eyesight go bad all of a sudden?
他的视力突然下降了吗？
Victim's ID info.
受害者的身份证信息
Answer, damn it.
接电话 该死
Good, very good. You found some tire tracks, great.
非常好  发现了一些轮胎痕迹  太好了
Finger prints, too. Well done.
还有指纹  干的漂亮
Footprints for the next murder, you say?
下次谋杀时再找个脚印  你说怎么样？
There's already an ongoing country-wide search for him.
已经在全国范围内搜寻他了
And what good is the search?
有什么用处吗？
He kills right under our noses.
他在我们眼皮底下杀人
If he was afraid of getting caught,
如果他害怕被抓住
he wouldn't lay his cards on the table.
绝对不会摊牌
He knows he won't be caught.
他知道他不会被抓到
So there's only one way to catch him:
因此  只有一种方法可以抓住他：
Find out why he's committing the murders.
找出他为什么要杀人
Otherwise you'll go door to door, asking to yourselves where he is.
不然你就挨家挨户自己去找他
Here.
给你
You, my office.
你来我办公室
I spoke with the prosecutor today.
我今天和检察官谈过了
He doesn't want you involved in this whatsoever.
他不想让你卷入这件事
He told me to take you out of this case.
让我把你调走
I said "Okay, but maybe the Nevra on the labels is a different person."
我说：“好吧  但也许标签上写的Nevra是另外一个人”
We must take precautions, he says.
他说们必须采取预防措施
He asks if there's a difference between Nevra and anybody else.
他问Nevra跟其他人是否有区别
I told him how much difference it made for me.
我告诉他你对我有多重要
I told him what a great police officer you can be.
我告诉他你可以成为一名伟大的警察
In conclusion, he told me to do what I must.
最后  他让我放手去做
Do you know what this means?
你知道这是意味着什么吗？
If the Nevra this killer is talking about...
如果凶手说的Nevra……
is the same Nevra sitting across the table right now,
和现在坐在我对面的Nevra是同一个人
and you learn about this, and don't tell me,
你知道  并且不告诉我
you can't be a police anymore.
你就不能再做警察了
Understood, Chief.
明白  长官
Good.
好的
Out.
出去吧
Thank you.
谢谢
I have an idea.
我有个主意
I'm going mad. I'm about to lose my mind.
我要疯了……
Where is this man?
他去哪了？
He left his phone, too.
还把手机留下了
He doesn't use it, anyway.
他不用手机
What's this book he asked you to buy so urgently?
他叫你这么急着买的那本书是什么书?
No idea.
不知道……
Life Is Traffic, by Nukhet Coban.
生活就是交通  作者：努赫特·科班（Nukhet Coban）
Hi. This is Agah's room, isn't it?
嗨  这是Agah的病房 对吗？
Agah, my boy.
老弟
What are you up to now?
你在干嘛呢？
Our department had this guy, Zekai.
我们部门有个叫Zekai的人
Such a sweet man.
真是个好人
He had a son who caught pneumonia.
他儿子得了肺炎
Very severe.
非常严重
Doctors said he wouldn't live. What could Zekai do?
医生说他儿子快不行了  但Zekai又能做什么呢？
He lost all hope on doctors.
他对医生失去希望了
He visited holy sepulchers, made offerings.
他拜访圣墓教堂  供奉祭品。
The boy they said would die, miraculously recovered.
那个医生说快死掉的孩子  竟然奇迹般恢复过来
Zekai, of course, went to make his offering.
当然了  Zekai又去供奉
He's made a vow to make nine paupers happy.
他发誓要让九个穷人幸福
Because his son was nine. Whatever...
因为他儿子才九岁  不管怎样……
He goes to a poor neighborhood.
他去了贫民窟
His money's ready.
带足了钱
He gives the money away.
他把钱送了出去
Makes nine paupers happy.
让九个穷人幸福起来
A tenth pauper appears. "I'm poor, too." he says.
但是第十个穷人出现了  说：“我也很穷！”
Zekai says he's out of money, but the guy won't believe him.
Zekai说他已经没有钱了  但是那人不相信他
"You gave a fortune away, where's mine?" he asks.
“你给出去了一大笔钱  我的呢？”他问
- And stabs Zekai. - Oh, dear.
-然后刺杀了Zekai -哦  天啊
Such a pity.
真的很遗憾
Yes, indeed.
确实
But then, you understand the tenth pauper.
但是  第十个穷人可以理解
Sure, sure.
是的
You give money to everybody, and when it's his turn...
你给所有人发钱  但轮到他时……
This happens sometimes. I mean...
这种情况时有发生  我是说……
There's a crime, but not a criminal.
这是犯罪  但他却不是罪犯
Hello there.
你好
Agah, sir? What are you doing here?
Agah  先生  您在这里做什么？
- Why? - Everyone's looking for you.
-怎么了？-每个人都在找你
- Has Zuhal left? - Who?
-Zuhal离开了吗？-谁？
- I'll go. - Were you staying here?
-我这就去 -你也住在这里吗？
- Agah, visit me some time! - Like hell I will. It's your fault.
-Agah  有空过来玩！-来个屁  都怪你！
Hello, Ates? Can you talk?
喂  Ates  你方便说话吗？
Yeah, I'm at work. At the department.
是的  我局里上班
There's this thing. Urgent. Could you come here?
有个急事  你能来一趟吗？
Nothing to worry about. Come. I'm waiting.
不用担心  来吧  我等你
- Sorry. I had a thing. - I'm sorry I couldn't come.
-对不起  我来晚了-对不起  我不能过去
To your department, I mean.
你的部门  我是说……
They don't like me over there.
你的同事不太喜欢我
It's as close as I can get.
我尽量帮你
This is for you.
这个给你
Thanks.
谢谢
It's cold, though.
有点凉了
I was like this.
我就是这样
Workaholic. Coffees went cold all the time.
工作狂  咖啡经常放凉
I may not look like it but I used to be
我可能看起来不像  但我曾经是
a fiery and an idealist reporter.
一位热情的理想主义者记者
I was a police reporter, too.
我也是一名警察记者
I don't about the fire,
我不热情
but there's still some idealism left.
但是还有一些理想主义
Otherwise why would you come all this way, no?
不然你为什么要大老远来  不是吗?
Maybe I just wanted to see you.
也许我只是想见你
Why not?
为什么不？
Maybe it's two birds with one stone. Why not?
也许是一石二鸟吧  为什么不呢？
Never.
不是的
As I am still carrying that idealism,
我仍然怀着理想主义
I am also carrying a stone for each bird.
我还为每只鸟背着一块石头
- What's this? - It's a story.
-这是什么？-是一篇文章
Can you publish it?
你可以出版吗？
"An anonymous law enforcement source."
“匿名执法来源”
- Exactly that. - Hmm.
-正是 -嗯
I gave you this. You're giving it back.
我给了你  你又还给了我
To me, that's romantic.
对我来说很浪漫
- The sooner the better. - All right.
-越快越好 -好的
I'll post it online.
我会在网上发布
Had a look at the courthouse yet?
你调查法院了吗
I did, but it's a dead end.
查了  但那是死胡同
Then I could send you to an entirely different street.
我可以送你去一条完全不同的街道
Your dead judge...
那个死掉的法官
All his cases involved some sort of bribery.
他经手的所有案件都涉及某种贿赂
Public knowledge, too.
众所周知
Might as well have invoiced them.
很可能都有发票
If you were to look at...
如果你想知道……
whose lives he'd ruined in those cases,
他在这些案件中毁掉了谁的生活
maybe you'll find something.
也许你会发现一些东西
But his record is spotless.
但是他的记录一尘不染
Then for one time only,
只有一次
he didn't take a bribe...
他没有受贿
But gave a bribe.
而是行贿
Use your other medicine. They won't cause a problem.
服用另外一种药  那样不会造成任何问题
But sir, you have to let your daughter know.
但是先生  你得让你的女儿知道
Yes, of course.
当然
I must accept it first.
我必须先接受
Then I'll tell them both.
然后再告诉他们两个
Alzheimer's is a serious condition.
老年痴呆症是很严重的病
Tailor-made for a serious man like myself.
为像我这样严肃的人量身定做的
Where were you this morning?
今天早上你在哪里？
Your daughter worried about you.
你的女儿很担心你
The night I had a heart attack,
我心脏病发作的那天晚上
I had a sharp pain right here.
我在这里剧烈疼痛
I said, "Agah, this is it. You're leaving this life."
我说：“Agah  就是这样  你将要走完这一生”
First thing I thought about
我首先想到的是
was what my daughter and grandson was going to do.
我女儿和孙子要怎么办
What would become of them?
他们会怎样？
So interesting.
很有趣
So long as man doesn't understand that he's dying,
如果人不知道自己快死了
he doesn't think about those he's leaving behind.
就不会去想他的后人
I called my lawyer.
我打电话给我的律师
Told him to leave them everything.
告诉他把一切都留给家人
They shouldn't have to deal with the inheritance stuff.
他们不必处理继承的事情
I was busy with those things.
早上我在忙那些事情
I didn't want to make them sad, and didn't tell them.
不想让他们难过  所以并没有告诉他们
Come in, please.
请进来吧
Let's get to the point.
我们言归正传
You'll be our guest for another day.
你要在我们这里多住一天
- Okay? - Okay.
- 好吗？好吧
- All right. Get well soon. - Thank you.
-好的  祝早日康复 -谢谢
You made us leave.
你让我们离开
I couldn't ask while he's here.
他在这里的时候我不能问
What's this thing you can't share with us?
什么事不能让我们听到？
You know about the heart attack I had, sweetie?
你知道我得了心脏病吧  亲爱的？
I asked the doctor about my sexual life this point on.
我刚才咨询医生一些关于性生活的问题
Now you know.
现在你知道了
Would you have liked to listen?
你想听吗？
I wish I could stay.
我想留下来
No, you go home and rest.
不  你回家休息
We'll be back tomorrow anyway.
我们明天还会回来
Dad called today.
爸爸今天打电话了
Finally, huh.
终于……
Finally he must've understand what he's done.
他总算想清楚他做了什么
Doesn't have the face to call me, either.
没脸给我打电话了
So he called you. What is he saying?
所以他打给你  他在说什么？
He filed for divorce.
他提出要离婚
Ah.
啊
That's a relief.
解脱了
Really. I'm relieved.
真的  我解脱了
I mean...
我是说……
That's a load off my shoulder.
我肩上的重担终于能放下了
I'm happy.
我很高兴
So happy.
很高兴
Finally, that's done.
终于结束了
- Mom, you're fine, right? - Why wouldn't I be?
-妈妈  你还好吧？-我为什么不好呢？
Good night.
晚安
That's not me.
不是我
It's some other Nevra Elmas.
是其他的Nevra Elmas
Or like Firuz had said,
或像Firuz所说的那样
he must have seen me on TV or the newspaper, and is addressing me.
他一定在电视或报纸上见过我  并且在跟我沟通
That may be. But the real question is
也许是这样  但真正的问题是
not whom he's writing, but why he's writing.
不是他在给谁写  而是他为什么在写
I think he's alone.
我觉得他很孤独
Crippling from it, in fact.
实际上是很严重的孤独
No one to speak with.
没人跟他说话
Even if he does, nobody's listening.
即使他说了  也没人听
He wants to be listened to so badly,
他非常渴望被倾听
he's willing to kill for it.
他愿意为此而杀人
MISSING SUSPECT
寻找嫌犯
Who could be that lonely?
谁会那么孤独？
Zuhal? Darling?
Zuhal？亲爱的？
Mister? Mister?
先生？先生？
Are you okay, mister?
先生  你还好吗？
- Peace be with you. - And also with you.
-和平与你同在 -也与你同在
What brought you here, at this hour?
这个时候来这里有什么事吗？
I've come to take my car. They towed it here.
我来取我的车  他们把车拖到这里了
Come tomorrow.
明天来
No. Tomorrow won't do.
明天不行的
I'm coming from the hospital. I have somebody sick.
我从医院过来的  我有个朋友生病了
I have to take the car there, and go to their hometown.
我必须要取车  然后开车去他家
I wish them well. Where are you from?
我希望他没事  你来自哪里？
- Mister. Are you feeling better? - Yeah.
-先生  您感觉好些吗？-是的
We've called an ambulance. They'll be here soon.
我们叫了一辆救护车他们很快到这里
What?
什么？
What are you saying?
你在说什么？
- In the car. - What's there?
-车里……-有什么？
In the bag...
在包里……
- What's there? - In the bag...
-里面有什么？-包里……
Mister...
先生……
- Mister. - In the car...
-先生 -在车上
- What? - My car.
-什么？-我的车
This second murder is really making national headlines.
第二起谋杀案已经成为全国头条新闻
While the nationwide search for the killer, Tufan Elibol, is still ongoing,
尽管在全国范围内搜寻杀手Tufan Elibol仍在进行中
it is believed that he may not be acting alone,
但人们相信他可能不是独自作案
and that he may have two or three accomplices.
可能有两个或三个同伙
According to the anonymous law enforcement source,
根据匿名执法来源
these murders may have nothing to do with Tufan Elibol.
这些谋杀可能与Tufan Elibol无关
Indeed, dear viewers, he may be a victim of them.
确实  他可能也是一名受害者
Hey!
嘿!
You sissy!
你个傻B！
I'll make you pay for this!
我会让你为此付出代价！
Bloody hell. Hey!
该死！嘿！
Screw this.
该死！
Fuck! Fuck this!
- Help! - What are you doing?
-救命！-你在做什么？
What are you doing? You'll break the elevator.
你在做什么？你快把电梯弄坏了
- Stop it. - Help!
-快停下 -救命！
Stop! You'll cut your hand. Don't bang on the glass.
停下来！你会割伤手的  不要在玻璃上敲打
Help me!
救命啊！
What are you doing? Why are you yelling for nothing?
你在做什么？你为什么无缘无故地喊？
Open it. I can't hear you, open this.
开门  我听不到你说话  开门
Sir, I beg you. Let me go, I won't go to the police.
先生  求求你放开我  我不会报警
- I'll go home. - Okay. That's what I'm saying.
-我要回家 -好的  我就是这么说的
- I beg you, sir. - If you'll let me finish...
-求求您  先生 -如果你让我把话说完
- Just... - I... Shut the hell up!
-求你…… -给我闭嘴！
Now...
好了……
The mechanic says...
修理工说
When the elevator is stuck between two floors,
当电梯卡在两层楼之间时
press on the call button once.
按下通话按钮一次
If it doesn't move,
如果它不动
it's something only the mechanic could fix.
那就是只有修理工能解决的问题
I can't kill you here.
我不能在这里杀了你
How will I remove your body?
那样怎么处理尸体呢？
Help me! Help!
救救我！
So, let me tell you how we'll do this.
好了  让我来说下怎么办
I'll press this button once.
我会按一次这个按钮
Just the one time.
只按一次
If it doesn't come down, you'll live.
如果不降下来，你就不会死
I'll go to the police, and that's that.
而我去警察局自首  就这样
What if it works?
如果它能运行了呢？
What if it comes down?
如果降下来会怎样？
Well...
那样的话……
Then...
那么……
I'll have to do something I won't like at all.
我就要做一些我不喜欢做的事情了
- I'll have to kill you. - Ah, man!
-我得杀了你 -啊  天啊！
Help!
救命！
I think Nevra spotted our ruse, anyway.
总之我认为Nevra发现了识破了我们的诡计
I don't really need you anymore.
我已经不需要你了
Very interesting.
很有意思
These things really do happen.
这些事情确实发生了
A turning point.
转折点
All right.
好吧
Well...
好
Are you ready?
你准备好了吗？
Can anybody hear me?
谁能听到吗？
Anybody?
有人吗
Come here. Fuck you.
过来，尼玛的！
- Help me! - I'm pressing the button.
-救救我！-我按下按钮
- Let's see how it goes. - Anybody!
-看看结果如何 -有人吗！
Pure luck.
全靠运气
- Can anybody hear me? - I'm pressing.
-有人听见吗 -我要按了哦
Fuck this.
该死！
Help!
救命！
No!
不要啊！
Think of your health.
想想你的身体状况
A little exercise won't kill you.
多做一些运动不会要你的命
Why are you in the elevator?
你为什么在电梯里？
Just use the stairs.
走楼梯不好吗
See?
你看
It's bad for the heart.
这样对心脏不好
Why aren't you answering?
你为什么不接电话？
That's why you've come?
我不接你就直接过来了？
Yes, mom.
是的  妈妈
How'd you like it, mom?
妈妈  你感觉如何？
Beautiful, isn't it?
很漂亮  不是吗？
You have a lovely room.
你有一个可爱的房间
I'll always call you.
我会经常打电话给你
Everyday.
每天都打
The director's here, madam.
主任来了  夫人
Mom, I'll speak to the director and be back.
妈  我跟主任聊一下就回来
Okay?
好吗？
- These should be with her. - Of course.
-这些应该和她在一起 -好的
Don't worry. We'll take good care of her.
不用担心  我们会好好照顾她的
- Thanks. You'll be here, then? - Yes. I'll help her move in.
-谢谢  那么你会在这里吗？-是的  我会帮助她安顿好
Mom, I'll be back soon.
妈  我马上回来
Oh, poor Agah.
哦  可怜的Agah
你做了什么？
What have you done?